

CONTACTS



Noida, India



ashnagupta122@gmail.com



8168307152

EDUCATION

M.Phil. (Clinical Psychology) Amity University, Lucknow 2022

P.G. Diploma (Guidance and Counseling)

Punjab University 2016

M.A. (Clinical and Counselling Psychology)

M.C.M. D.A.V. College for Women, Panjab University 2015

B.A. (Psychology)

Kurukshetra University 2013

CERTIFICATES

- Neurobiofeedback-NIMHANS.2020
- **CBT Practitioner** Psychowaves and Punjab University, 2019
- Teach LD- ODE,2016
- Intelligence and Neuropsychological Assessment- Psychowaves, 2016

EXPERTISE

- CBT, REBT, ACT
- Schema Therapy
- Group Therapy
- Systems Therapy
- Family Therapy

Ashna Gupta

Clinical Psychologist

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Over a **6-year career** in the field of mental health, working in the northern region of India, Ashna has played an essential role in providing mental health services to children, adolescents, and adults in need of rehabilitation and psychological education. The motto that has driven her work all these years in psychology hasn't changed: Paying close attention to needs of clients, spotting behavior patterns, and iterating from there. With vigorous training and learning in administering psychological assessments as well as psychotherapeutic approaches especially schema-based, system-oriented and acceptance-based therapies, she believes in creating and maintaining a value-based practice.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Clinical Psychologist

March, 2023-Present The Hans Foundation, Gurgaon

Conducted comprehensive psychological profiling, implemented integrated therapeutic solutions with a focus on family support, and delivered life skills training for individuals with disabilities in rural communities of Noida, Uttar Pradesh.

Counseling Psychologist

Nov,2018-Nov,2020

M.M. Medical College and Hospital, Solan, H.P.

- Through psychiatric interviews, administered programs of treatment after evaluating mental and emotional disorders of individuals
- Administered and interpreted intelligence, personality, or other psychological tests to support evaluation and conceptualizing cases.
- **Documented therapy** in accordance with policies and procedures regarding medical records

Consultant Psychologist

Dec,2019-Nov,2020

YourDost, Online Counseling Platform

- Scheduled sessions with clients regularly to provide psychotherapeutic treatment and adjust treatment plans as necessary
- Provided **crisis intervention** in situations requiring immediate psychological treatment.
- Referred clients for offline therapy when necessary

School Counselor

Oct,2017-Nov,2018

Cambridge International School for Girls, Jalandhar, Punjab.

- Advised and counseled adolescents (11-15 years) regarding shortterm social and emotional problems to build self-esteem and resilience using schema based approaches.
- Provided academic guidance in order to develop higher educational and career aspirations among adolescents
- Early identification of problem behaviors with age group (2-10 years) and took suitable steps to prevent the onset of psychosocial problems
- Closely worked with parents and teachers to provide a system based evaluation and intervention. Also, taught psychology as an additional subject to 11th and 12th grades.